One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Until I can reach the sky,
I believe, until the next tomorrow, hey
Chasing and being chased on top of Mobius' ring.
Getting closer and facing forward, hey I want to share your style.
It begins, it expands, this flavor that exceeds imagination
I feel so good throughout my body, I will become free, oh yeah
Share the music, even if it's far.
Share the one dream, by telling each other.
Share the good times and laugh.
I'll keep going until I can reach the sky.
Let's overcome it now, I believe in the next tomorrow yeah yeah...
You were waiting there on the other side of the invisible wall.
I'll be there soon, I believe in one world yeah yeah...
Alright...
Now it's my turn to go full-power too.
Gear Second!
What is that?!
Smoke's coming from his body!
Is that how men are?!
In that case, I'll bite you to death
with all the power I have too!
Medusa Hair...
Eight-Headed Serpent!
Go!
Sandersonia-sama!
The fence around the arena!
The giant serpents are actually her hair,
yet it's like they have fangs of iron!
Why can't I hit him?!
I'm reading his every move ahead of time,
but I can't keep up!
Rubber...
It's no use!
Your attacks bounce right off,
as I showed you before!
Jet...
Bazooka!
Sonia! Mari!
What are you two playing around for?!
B-Big Sis...!
S-Sorry, Big Sis!
We'll finish him at once!
She's on fire!
Medusa Hair...
Salamander!
We won't give you anywhere to run!
He's surrounded!
There's no escape now,
no matter how nimble he is!
There's no better attack than this!
Rubber...
Jet...
Gatling!
Oh no!
Big Sis Sonia! Get away, quickly!
What?! I'm being dragged!
Our tails! When did he...?!
It's hot! It's hot! Help!
Wait, Big Sis! Don't pull me!
Big Sis Sonia! Watch out!
That's the pit of blades!
Hold on to the stands!
Th-That was close...
S-Sandersonia-sama?!
Ouch! Hot!
He's kicking her when she's down!
He's inhuman!
He's going to knock Sonia-sama
into the pit and skewer her!
Damn you, man!
Don't move!
Even if you guys wanna kill me,
I don't wanna kill you!
You insolent little...!
Mari! Use this chance to kill him!
What are you doing, Mari?!
I can't, Big Sis Sonia...!
Because...
he's protecting us right now...!
Look! Sandersonia-sama's
clothing burned off
and her back is showing!
If that man gets off her,
her Gorgon Eyes will be exposed!
Oh no!
Everyone who sees them
will be turned to stone!
My back...!
You guys said so earlier!
We would rather die than let anyone see what you saw on my back!
You'd rather die than let
people see this, right?!
So don't move!
The combat is over!
Everyone leave the arena at once before you're exposed to the Gorgon Eyes!
Oh no! We gotta get outside!
We'll be petrified!
Hurry! Hurry!
The Gorgon's curse!
I was fighting you just moments ago.
Why are you protecting me?
What you don't want to be seen has nothing to do with our fight.
Hancock's Confession
We're sorry, Big Sis!
We're sorry that we lost and
had to be saved by our enemy.
Are you up next?
That's enough.
I don't feel like it.
Oh, yeah?
I hope that she's not damaged.
Alright then,
these people you turned to stone;
turn them back.
You can do something, right?
They were just trying to defend me!
They didn't do anything wrong!
Hey, please?!
Yes, indeed,
I can revert them if I want.
But...
You said that you want
to go someplace by ship.
Yes, my crew's waiting for me.
Oh, that's nice.
But I can only make
one of your wishes come true.
It's either revert them
or help you to get off this island.
Choose one wish and give up on the other!
Reveal your true nature, Man.
That's great! Thank you!
That means you're going to help them, right?
Thank you... very much!!
He doesn't hesitate at all.
How is it that a man who has such great Haki
bows his head in order
to save his benefactors...
Coliseum Exit
Marguerite!
Sweetpea!
Aphelandra!
Oh, here you all are!
Great! She turned you back from stone!
I was so worried because you
suddenly started to vouch for him.
She's right.
I was afraid of what would happen to you.
Turned us back?
What happened to us?
I have absolutely no recollection.
Don't you remember?
No I don't...
The next thing I knew, that man
was there and he was really happy.
Oh, I'm so relieved!
I was worried that you were going to die.
No one's here...
Is it all finished now?
...And that was it.
Looks like your memory from right before and after you were turned to stone is gone.
We'll tell you what happened after that.
Marguerite.
What happened to the man?
What about Snake Princess?
Did she turn him to stone this time?
I don't know that much,
but it seems like he got
summoned to the Kuja Castle.
What?!
Amazon Lily,
Kuja Castle
Hey, I want to know!
What do you want from me?
Oh!
Is there a meal after the battle?
If that's what it is, I'll be happy!
The Princess's Hall
We really need to thank you...
You have our gratitude.
Nah, it's fine.
It's not like I can eat your gratitude.
If anybody had seen what's on our backs,
there is no way that we
could stay in this country.
You may come in.
Come inside, Man.
Inside?
Inside of the curtain.
Oh, is that where the food is?
I'm coming...
Oh, we're not eating.
Hey, what are you doing
with your clothes off?
As always, you are reacting rudely.
Very well...
This is the mark...
that you said...
you had seen somewhere.
Take a good look at it, again.
Where did you see this?
Do you know the meaning of this mark?
Answer me, now!
It's not something I want to show people.
As I suspected, it's a bit different
from what I've seen before.
I have a friend called Hachi
who is a fish-man...
And he has a similar mark on his forehead so I thought it was the same.
I don't know anything about your mark.
If he doesn't know, why don't you tell him?
Granny Nyon!
Where did you come in from?
Be honest, Snake Princess.
You have seen clearly
how tolerant that man is.
Don't be afraid.
Tell him everything that you want to share.
You!
You are a pirate,
Monkey D. Luffy, am I right?
Yes, I am.
How do you know about me?
How can you be so casual after you caused such a sensation in the world?
Look at this newspaper!
Just the other day,
on the Sabaody Archipelago, close to the world's Center of Power,
this man attacked a Celestial Dragon!
That's an act that only one who does not fear the wrath of gods would perform!
A Celestial Dragon?!
In response to this, the government dispatched their greatest military forces, but he miraculously escaped.
After that incident,
he somehow made it to our distant kingdom in a mere two days!
It's all beyond our understanding.
I'm telling you, I was sent flying all of a sudden!
I have no idea where this place is!
And I don't regret attacking that Celestial Dragon.
Do you know that bastard did to my friends?
Then, that means...
You really did stand up to the Celestial Dragons?
So...
Such a fool...
still existed in this world?
Someone who would defy the heavens with no regard for his own life...
just like he did!
Who are you talking about?
I will tell you everything...
Even the meaning behind the symbol branded into your friend's forehead.
Hachi's mark?
This is...
the Hoof of the Dragon Galloping Across the Heavens...
The crest of the Celestial Dragons!
It is burned onto the flesh of those bought by the World Nobles.
It is a symbol that will never disappear, forever marking the bearer as less than human!
The Celestial Dragons?
We three sisters...
were once...
slaves of the World Nobles!
You were... slaves?!
It happened when I was twelve years old...
I bet you're hungry! I brought a snack!
Hancock?
Sonia! Mari! Where are you?
Three of us were taken
from the Kuja pirate ship...
...and we were sold!
Everything after that...
is a disgusting past which I do not wish to be reminded of.
The first men I ever saw in my life were a terrifying crowd...
Sister Sonia, calm down!
The memories haunts us...
W-Wow! H-Hey! That's enough!
Don't force yourselves! You don't have to tell me!
It was awful.
There was no hope.
We kept thinking about death!
Hey! You...
But...
...one night four years later,
something happened that made
the World Government tremble.
Nobody dared stand against the Celestial Dragons.
That was an undisputed law.
But then came a man who climbed the Red Line bare-handed,
and snuck into the Holy Land Mariejoa, home of the Celestial Dragons.
He was an adventurer who would one day come to command an entire crew of fishman pirates...
Fisher Tiger.
He entered the city responsible for so much cruelty towards his fellow fishmen,
and razed it to the ground in order to free the fishman slaves.
We are free! We are free!
He disliked humans as a species
but he was being fair to all slaves,
and let thousands of slaves
of different species go free.
We prepared to die and ran among the others.
We owe him an immeasurable debt.
Tiger released many fish-men to the sea,
but ones who were slaves had
a mark that cannot be erased.
Tiger has made the World Government his enemy
and he formed the
Sun Pirates with former slaves
and sailed out into the open sea.
As though breaking a curse,
he changed the Celestial Dragon's
emblem on everyone's bodies...
...into the symbol of the sun.
What you thought was similar
to the mark on my back is
the sun symbol of the Sun Pirates.
Yeah, you're right.
The one Hachi has on his
forehead looks like the sun.
Does that mean he was a slave, too?
It doesn't necessarily mean that he was.
The mark is made in such a way
that it is impossible to tell...
...whether they are former slaves or not.
I'm pretty sure that he once was
a member of the Sun Pirates.
In fact, Fisher Tiger is already dead and...
...the Sun Pirates have split
up into several groups.
I guess Hachi has led a complicated life, too...
So this is the reason
that the mark on our backs
is similar to the fish-men's mark.
Okay, I pretty much understand.
Ironically, the Devil Fruits we were given as slaves to entertain our masters,
the Love Fruit and the Snake Fruits,
were what made it possible for us to deceive the country and protect our secret.
If you didn't cover up
Sonia's back at that moment,
it would have been impossible
for us to stay on this island.
I don't want to let anyone
know about our past!
Even if it means deceiving the entire kingdom...
We must never let our guard down for as long as we live!
We will never be slaves again!
The idea of being at someone else's mercy...
It is too frightening for me to endure...!
Big Sister...
Ho!
But this is the first time in a long time
since you were this sincere about your own feelings.
I was actually wondering if your heart had turned to ice by now.
Be silent, you traitor who abandoned the kingdom!
You are the one who should be silent!
After you had been freed from the Celestial Dragons,
you were just a defenseless little girl...
Wandering around, and not knowing how to return to the island!
Who do you think it was who brought you all the way back here?!
You should be thankful that
I was living outside of this country!
You try to change my mind because of such a small debt?
What did you say?!
Granny Nyon...
I always keep an eye on
you three as a mother would!
Do you...
hate me, now that you know that I was a slave?
I told you, I hate the Celestial Dragons!
I've taken a liking to you!
Didn't you say that you had one more wish?
All right!
Where do you want to go?
I'll give you a ride!
For real?!
Departure will be tomorrow morning.
The Kuja Pirates will give you a
ride to the Sabaody Archipelago.
--What?! By our pirate ship?
--Sorry to be a pain!
Rest well tonight to prepare for tomorrow.
I can't wait to get off this island tomorrow!
Why can't you get it? It's like this!
Like this! This!
This!
Is it like this?
That's so funny, Luffy-sama!
Men stick chopsticks in their nasal cavities
to their mouth
and hold baskets in their hand...
What a classless dance!
Rubber... Belly-talk!
This is the specialty of Maiden Island!
What? Specialty?
Penne gorgonzola with Sea King meat.
I often eat Sea King meat
but this is different!
It really does stretch!
It's soft like gum!
Your time's up!
--What? One more time!
--No, then you won't stop!
Wow, this Sea King meat is
very good! It's hard to eat...
W-W-What are you doing - picking
and stretching my body?!
We can't help it! You'll
leave tomorrow, right?
There are a lot of people who
want to touch you just one time.
See!
"20 gol per touch"
--You're so popular!
--Luffy-chan!
You can't do business using
me without asking me!!
Come on, Luffy-chan! Tonight is
our only chance to touch a man!
Hey! S-Stop, you people!
I can't eat! Hey! Hey!
Where's Marguerite?
--Where did Luffy-sama go?
--No! He ran away!
He can't have gotten too far!
Let's find him and touch him!
What's the matter with them?
Keep hiding!
This is the only food that I could bring.
It's great that you can
return to your friends!
Yeah. Well, I'm sorry that
I got you into some trouble.
I worried when you turned into stone!
But you protected us, right?
I heard what happened.
Thank you, Luffy!
What's the matter, Marguerite?
Luffy's been chased by girls of the village.
No wonder. They don't see men often.
Hey, Granny Bean!
This part of the village is
secluded. Stay here for a while.
And my name's not Bean!!
He has something to eat, so just
bring him tea or something.
Okay.
Granny, you like to read newspapers, huh?
The News Coos don't deliver to the Calm Belt,
so it's hard to get these.
The empress of this kingdom is a Warlord of the Sea,
I have to know what's going
on in the world at least.
Who's a Warlord of the Sea?
Snake Princess.
What?!
She's a Warlord of the Sea?
Does that mean she's
really strong in a fight?
You are a pirate.
Didn't you notice it?
N-No, I didn't.
Don't you read newspapers?
No, I don't read them.
Oh, what a shock!
Snake Princess became
empress of this country
and a captain of the
Kuja Pirates 11 years ago.
She was still so young, but after just one voyage, a bounty of 80 million was put on her head.
Just one voyage?
It had to do with the bad reputation
Kuja had even before her.
The World Government became
cautious about her from the start
and they suggested that she become
one of the Seven Warlords.
But now, that title is about to be revoked.
W-What?!
The Seven Warlords and Navy Headquarters
are gonna fight
the Whitebeard Pirates?!
What's that?! What'll happen?!
W-W-W-W-Wait a minute!
T-This is too much to hear at once!
What a foolish man!
You don't know anything.
I must say, that was just a prediction.
But the battle will probably happen.
The World Government has made a move.
Whitebeard is a man who would never
allow his mates to be killed.
Even though they know this, they
announced the public execution of...
Portgas D. Ace, a great
commander of Whitebeard's.
Of who?
Ace. "Fire Fist" Ace.
What's wrong?
Ace... is gonna get executed?
I heard a pirate called Blackbeard...
...became a Warlord of the Sea by
defeating "Fire Fist" Ace.
Blackbeard...
The World Government will take full
advantage of this big fish they've caught,
a pirate named Ace...
Granny...
Granny!!
He's my brother!
Ace is my older brother!
What?!
Is that true?! He's your brother?!
I didn't know that he was captured.
And he's gonna be executed?!
Then, there's no chance for him to escape!
If Whitebeard wins this battle,
there will be a chance for him.
What should I do? Where are
they gonna execute him?
It'll take place Marinford's town square,
where Navy Headquarters stands.
It says "in one week," which
means 6 days from today.
What?! That's too soon!
How long will it take to get to
Sabaody Archipelago from here?
It will take more than a week.
If it takes that long, then Ace will
be finished before I meet my crew!
Then how long will it take
to get to where Ace is?
Impel Down is where he locked, and
it'll take a week by a pirate ship
and 4 days by a navy ship.
Why?! Navy ships are that fast?
There's a current used exclusively
by the World Government.
Enies Lobby.
Impel Down.
Navy Headquarters.
There's a giant whirlpool which
connects those three facilities.
When you open the Gate of Justice
at any of the three facilities,
the current runs inside
allowing you to enter.
That means if the gates aren't open,
you'd just keep drifting on the current.
Pirate ships would rather avoid the current by going a long way round.
What should I do?
What do you want to do?
Don't tell me that's your
brother's Vivre Card!
Oh, is it the sheet that moves
around that you care about so much?
That's a different one.
This is the one that Ace gave to me.
That's also known as a paper of life.
It tells you a direction in which the
person is and about their vital energy.
So, if it's that small, it means...
When I got it, it was ten times bigger.
Ace has his own adventure...
It's natural for a big brother to worry about...
his bungling kid brother.
Ace won't like me rescuing him
since he's stronger.
But...
I'm sorry, everybody.
I'm gonna take a little side trip.
I wanna go and rescue Ace!
Do you have any idea how reckless it would be and how big this battle is going to be?
You'll be like an ant blown into a storm.
You can just be flicked away
without even having done anything.
I don't care what's gonna
happen! I just wanna go!
I can't just sit by calmly on the
sidelines and let this happen!
I see.
So you're going to rescue the most
infamous prisoner in the world now.
If there is a chance in a million,
you better go to the Great
Prison where he's being held.
When they move him to the
execution ground in Marinford,
the navy admirals and the Seven
Warlords will be keeping a close eye.
However, because your brother is now
the most important prisoner they have,
there is no doubt that they're guarding the
prison with the military's full strength.
So it's impossible to enter.
I care more about getting there in
time than what happens after.
I got to get there while Ace is there.
Just give me a big oar,
and I'll paddle myself...
Wait a second! You can't
get there on will alone.
This is a slim chance, too, but...
Snake Princess refuses to follow the order to
force the Seven Warlords to assemble.
If only she obeys the order,
we can take advantage of it
and let you on their ship.
Their ship? There's a navy ship here?!
Then I'm gonna go and ask her!
Amazon Lily
Kuja Castle
Granny Nyon!
What's wrong, Enishida? Why
are you in such a hurry?
Thank god. I was going to come get you.
What happened?
Well...
Snake Princess...
has come down with an unknown illness.
--She's sick?!
--Oh my god!
Big Sis! Hang in there!
Big Sis!
Oh, Granny Nyon!
You, wait outside for a while.
What?! But I have to hurry!
I know that!
I can't breathe.
The way she's clutching her chest,
I think there's something
wrong with her heart.
But I can't figure out what it is.
I've never seen symptoms like these, so
I don't know what to prescribe.
Snake Princess seems to be in a lot of pain.
She didn't eat a thing.
Tomorrow morning...
--Snake Princess!
--Granny Nyon, stop fooling around with her!
Of course!
I can't believe this!
What an untimely virus!
--A virus?
--Do you know what it is?
Granny Nyon... I can't breathe!
Am I... going to die?
Yes, you are.
--What're you saying?!
--Stop making stupid jokes, Granny Nyon!
The former empress died
from the same illness.
I heard the empress before
that died from this, too.
I caught it, too, but left this country and survived.
Snake Princess, Monkey D. Luffy is here with me.
Hey, Granny Nyon!
He wants to ask you a favor.
Can you at least listen to him?
--Big Sis is suffering!
--What are you thinking?!
She's standing!
Alright. I'd like to hear it.
How lucky he is, Monkey D. Luffy!
Will he move this mountain
that no one could move?!
Did you want something? Luffy?
I gotta ask you something!
Are you alright?
No sickness can overtake me.
There's a Whitebeard pirate named Ace who's
waiting to be executed. He's my brother!
I want to rescue Ace!
But I heard a pirate ship
can't make it in time!
Can you board the navy ship and take me to Ace's prison?!
How self-centered can
you be? Straw Hat Luffy!
You know Big Sis's pain but you still
ask her to go to that abhorrent place?!
How cruel you are!
We showed you mercy and then you become arrogant!
This is why we hate men! Big Sis's
patience is wearing very thin!
Turn him to stone and
throw him over the edge!
So you want me to follow their order for
the Seven Warlords to convene.
--Big Sis!
--Kill him!
If you want me to...
I'll go anywhere!
Good! Thank you! This way I can
make it before the execution!
S-Snake Princess decided to
go to the World Government HQ!
What happened to her, Granny Nyon?!
The Snake Princess is
suffering from love sickness!
The former empresses died
from being burnt by love!
There is a saying around the East Blue:
"Love is always..."
"...a hurricane!"
Translation, Funimation
Soundtracking, Halee
Editing, Sewil, Feeso
Infoboxes/title card, BernieCrane
Timing, Sewil
Quality checking, Galaxy 9000, alasta, Mr. Luffy